Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Index: W23. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - General Administration & Staff - Discounts on Personal Computers., 1984. (Box 391, Folder 3)
- Index: W23. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - General Administration & Staff., 1979-1981. (Box 391, Folder 4)
- Index: W23. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - General Administration & Staff., 1978-1981. (Box 391, Folder 5)
- Index: W23/P6. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - General Administration & Staff - General Computing Plans., 1984-1986. (Box 391, Folder 6)
- Index: W23/P6. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - General Administration & Staff - General Computing Plans., 1976-1984. (Box 392, Folder 1)
- Index: W23/P6. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - General Administration & Staff - General Computing Plans., 1978-1980. (Box 392, Folder 2)
- Index: W23/P6. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - General Administration & Staff - General Computing Plans., 1976-1977. (Box 392, Folder 3)
- Index: W24. Instructional Units - Campus Computing - Purchasing., 1968-1992. (Box 392, Folder 4)
- Index: W25. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems (AIS) - General., 1992-1996. (Box 392, Folder 5)
- Index: W25. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems (AIS) - General., 1982-1995. (Box 392, Folder 6)
- Index: W25. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems (AIS) - General., 1978-1986. (Box 392, Folder 7)
- Index: W26. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems (AIS) - Administration & Staff., 1978-1994. (Box 393, Folder 1)
- Index: W26/A3. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - AIS - Administration & Staff - Administrative Computing Committee., 1978-1994. (Box 393, Folder 2)
- Index: W26/M4. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - AIS - Administration & Staff - UCLA/DPC South Merger Conversion to AIS 3031., 1977-1982. (Box 393, Folder 3)
- Index: W26/M4. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - AIS - Administration & Staff - UCLA/DPC South Merger Conversion to AIS 3031., 1978-1979. (Box 393, Folder 4)
- Index: W28/F5. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - AIS - Systems - Financial Systems., 1986-1997. (Box 393, Folder 5)
- Index: W28/F5. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Systems - Financial Systems., 1979-1988. (Box 393, Folder 6)
- Index: W28/F5. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - AIS - Systems - Financial Systems., 1978-1980. (Box 393, Folder 7)
- Index: W28/S8. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administrative Information Systems (AIS) - Student Systems., 1980-1985. (Box 394, Folder 1)
- Index: W28/S8. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing-Administrative Information Systems(AIS)- Systems-Student Systems., 1983-1996. (Box 394, Folder 2)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units- Campus Computing - Academic Technolgy Service (Previously Office of Academic Computing)-General., 1993-1994. (Box 394, Folder 3)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units- Campus Computing- Academic Technolgy Service (Before Office of Acad Computing)-General(Includes Social Science Computing)., 1986-1993. (Box 394, Folder 4)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units- Campus Comuting-Academic Technology Service (Prev Office of Acad Computing)-Gen-(Includes Physical Sci Computing Committ)., 1983-1988. (Box 394, Folder 5)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units- Campus Comuting-Academic Technology Service (Previously Office of Acad Computing)-General (IBM 3090 System)., 1985-1986. (Box 394, Folder 6)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Acaemic Technology Services (Previously Office of Academic Computing) - General - (Social Sci Comp)., 1984-1986. (Box 395, Folder 1)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Academic Technology Services - General (Incl: GSM Computing Facility)., 1986. (Box 395, Folder 2)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Academic Technology Services - General - (Sch of Med Computing)., 1985-1986. (Box 395, Folder 3)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Academic Technology Services - General., 1984-1986. (Box 395, Folder 4)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Academic Technology Services - General - (GSM Computing Facility)., 1983-1985. (Box 395, Folder 5)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Academic Technology Services - General - (Social Science Computing)., 1982-1984. (Box 395, Folder 6)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Academic Technology Service (previously Office of Academic Computing) - General., 1982-1984. (Box 396, Folder 1)
- Index: W29. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Academic Technology Service (previously Office of Academic Computing) - General., 1978-1981. (Box 396, Folder 2)
- Index: W30. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administration and Staff., 1978-1993. (Box 396, Folder 3)
- Index: W30. Instructional Support Units - Campus Computing - Administration and Staff - (Includes budget/rates)., 1980-1985. (Box 396, Folder 4)
- Index: Y25. Public Service - Department of Fine Arts Production - Ticket Office (includes CTO Services to Public Affairs, CTO Survey #2)., 1984-1990. (Box 396, Folder 5)
- Index: Y25-01. Public Service - Department of Fine Arts Production - Ticket Office - CTO Expansion., 1984-1990. (Box 396, Folder 6)
- Index: Y25. Public Service - Department of Fine Arts Production - Ticket Office - CTO Survey., 1985-1987. (Box 396, Folder 7)
- Index: Y25. Public Service - Department of Fine Arts Production - Ticket Office (Includes CTO Deficit, CTO Proposal)., 1976-1986. (Box 396, Folder 8)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General., 1990-1997. (Box 397, Folder 1)
- Index: YB1-02. Public Service - University Extension - General - CUCC Review., 1979-1995. (Box 397, Folder 2)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General (Includes UCLA Malibu Conference Center)., 1984-1989. (Box 397, Folder 3)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General - Hotel Conference Center., 1986-1988. (Box 397, Folder 4)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General., 1978-1988. (Box 397, Folder 5)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General - Hotel Conference Center., 1984-1986. (Box 397, Folder 6)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General., 1982-1985. (Box 398, Folder 1)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General (Hotel/Conference Center)., 1981-1984. (Box 398, Folder 2)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General (Hotel/Conference Center)., 1980. (Box 398, Folder 3)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General (Hotel/Conference Center)., 1973-1980. (Box 398, Folder 4)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General (Policy on Part-Time Off Campus Prof Grad Degree Programs)., 1977-1979. (Box 398, Folder 5)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General (UNEX Review)., 1977-1978. (Box 398, Folder 6)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - General (Includes Systemwide Study Committee on UNEX)., 1971-1978. (Box 399, Folder 1)
- Index: YB1. Public Service - University Extension - (From Academic Planning and Budget Office files)., 1968-1974. (Box 399, Folder 2)
- Index: YB1/E8. Extended University (Files from Academic Planning and Budget)., 1973-1974. (Box 399, Folder 3)
- Index: YB1/E8. Extended University (Files from Academic Planning and Budget)., 1972-1973. (Box 399, Folder 4)
- Index: YB1/E8P. Extended University - President's Task Force on the Extended University (Files from Academic Planning and Budget)., 1971-1972. (Box 399, Folder 5)
- Index: YB1/E8-Prog. Extended University Programs (Architecture, Education, Human Service, Liberal Studies, Spanish, Public Health) (File from APB)., 1972-1976. (Box 399, Folder 6)
- Index: YB1/E8. Extended University (Academic Planning and Budget Office File) - Extended Unit Pilot Prog Student Questionnaire FW 1972/73 Baseline Marginal., 1972-1973. (Box 400, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1975-1980. (Box 401, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Marketing/Descente., 1975-1980. (Box 401, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1977-1980. (Box 401, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1976-1977. (Box 401, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1976-1977. (Box 401, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1971-1975. (Box 401, Folder 6)
- Index: RF19-01. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Governance., 1978-1980. (Box 402, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1981-1982. (Box 402, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Marketing/Descente., 1981-1982. (Box 402, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association ( Select Committees)., 1982. (Box 402, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1981-1983. (Box 402, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1982-1983. (Box 403, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Select Committee)., 1982-1983. (Box 403, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1983. (Box 403, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1981-1983. (Box 403, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities-Intercollegiate Athletics-National Collegiate Athletic Assoc.-Select Cte on Athletic Problems & Concerns in Athletics., 1983. (Box 403, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-01. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Governance., 1981-1984. (Box 403, Folder 6)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1983-1984. (Box 404, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1984 May-August. (Box 404, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National CollegiateAthletic Association (Includes - NCAA Championships & Rating Stats)., 1984 January-October. (Box 404, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1984 August-November. (Box 404, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - 1984 NCAA Championships at UCLA., 1981-1985. (Box 404, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1988. (Box 405, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19-02. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1985-1988. (Box 405, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees., 1988. (Box 405, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-09. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Financial Aid for Student Athletes., 1988-1989. (Box 405, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committee (minutes, etc)., 1988-1989. (Box 405, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association -1987-88 National Study of Intercollegiate Athl., 1988-1989. (Box 405, Folder 6)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association-16-Proposed Legislation:-18-NCAA Committees., 1989. (Box 406, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees., 1990. (Box 406, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Certification Program., 1990. (Box 406, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Certification Program., 1990. (Box 406, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees., 1990. (Box 406, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Certificate Program., 1990. (Box 407, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Serv. and Activities Intercollegiate Athletics-National Collegiate Athletic Assoc. (Includes RF19-20 - Financial Analysis of Intecol. Athlet)., 1977-1991. (Box 407, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Reporting Requirements., 1986-1991. (Box 407, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees., 1991. (Box 407, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Includes National Youth Sports Program)., 1972-1991. (Box 407, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committes., 1991. (Box 407, Folder 6)
- Index: RF19-16. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Proposed Legislation., 1991. (Box 408, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Certification Program., 1991. (Box 408, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Includeds -18 NCAA Committees)., 1991-1992. (Box 408, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees., 1992. (Box 408, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-01. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Governance., 1985-1992. (Box 408, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-16. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Proposed Legislation., 1991-1992. (Box 408, Folder 6)
- Index: RF19-11. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Freshman Academic Eligibility., 1989-1992. (Box 408, Folder 7)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees., 1992. (Box 408, Folder 8)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1992. (Box 409, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19-04. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Reporting Requirements., 1991-1993. (Box 409, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - (Dick Schultz/University of Virgina Case)., 1993. (Box 409, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-04. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Reporting Requirements., 1993. (Box 409, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-27. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees 1993. (Box 409, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-24. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Football Playoffs., 1984-1993. (Box 409, Folder 6)
- Index: RF19-27. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Committees -1993., 1993-1994. (Box 410, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Includes RF19-29 Search for Exec Dir 1993-94)., 1991-1994. (Box 410, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19-26. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National CollegiateAthletic Association - Black Coaches Issues., 1993-1994. (Box 410, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-24. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Football Playoffs., 1993-1994. (Box 410, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-24. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Football Playoffs., 1994. (Box 410, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-24. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Football Playoffs., 1994. (Box 411, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Certification Program., 1992-1994. (Box 411, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Certification Program., 1994. (Box 411, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Includes RF19-28 1994 NCAA Committee)., 1993-1994. (Box 411, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-33. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Gender Equity., 1993-1994. (Box 412, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Certification Program., 1994. (Box 412, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19-02. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA & TV., 1988-1995. (Box 412, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-16. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Conventions., 1987-1995. (Box 412, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-24. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association-Football Playoffs., 1994-1995. (Box 412, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-22. Student Services and Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1994-1995. (Box 412, Folder 6)
- Index: RF19. Student Services and Activities-Intercollegiate Athletics-National Collegiate Athletic Assoc. (Includes-16 (Proposed Legislation)+ -30 (Bowl Alliance)., 1993-1995. (Box 412, Folder 7)
- Index: RF19. Stud.Serv.& Act.-Intercollegiate Athletics-NCAA(Inc. Postseason Games; NCAA Committees-1981- 1986 Minutes Etc.)., 1981-1985. (Box 413, Folder 1)
- Index: RF19. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association - NCAA Conventions., 1976-1986. (Box 413, Folder 2)
- Index: RF19. Stud. Serv. & Activities-Intercollegiate Athletics-NCAA (Inc.: Academic Standards, Presidents Commission Precis)., 1982-1987. (Box 413, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - NCAA - Freshman Eligibility (Academic)., 1983-1988. (Box 413, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19-18. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - NCAA - NCAA Committees (Minutes, Agenda, Membership)., 1987-1988. (Box 413, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1985-1998. (Box 413, Folder 6)
- Index: BH4. Uni. Admin. & Acad. Senate - Medical & Health Sciences Coordination - 10 Year Plan for Med. & Health Sciences., 1970-1994. (Box 414, Folder 1)
- Index: BI. Universitywide Administration & Academic Senate - Planning., 1974. (Box 414, Folder 2)
- Index: BT4. Universitywide Administration & Academic Senate - University Relations - Alumni Relations., 1978-1996. (Box 414, Folder 3)
- Index: RF19-25. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - NCAA - NCAA Restructuring., 1993-1997. (Box 414, Folder 4)
- Index: RF19. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - NCAA (Includes -03 NCAA Championships held at UCLA)., 1987-1996. (Box 414, Folder 5)
- Index: RF19-04. Student Services & Activities - Intercollegiate Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1993-1995. (Box 414, Folder 6)
- Index: V10. Instructional Units - Programmatic Review - (Uniwide Prog. Review - Admin., Business, Mgmt.)., 1982. (Box 415, Folder 1)
- Index: V10. Instructional Units - Programmatic Review - (Universitywide Program Review - Foreign Languages., 1982-1983. (Box 415, Folder 2)
- Index: V10. Instructional Units - Programmatic Reviews - Universitywide Program Review - Foreign Languages., 1983. (Box 415, Folder 3)
- Index: V10. Instructional Units - Programmatic Reviews - Universitywide Program Review - Education., 1984-1986. (Box 415, Folder 4)
- Index: V10. Instructional Units - Programmatic Review., 1988. (Box 415, Folder 5)
- Index: VA1. Instructional Units - School of Architecture & Urban Planning - General, Administration & Budget., 1958-1984. (Box 415, Folder 6)
- Index: VA1. Instructional Units - School of Architecture & Urban Planning - General, Administration & Staff., 1979-1986. (Box 416, Folder 1)
- Index: VA1-01. Instructional Units - School of Architecture & Urban Planning - General, Administration & Budget - Budget., 1978-1990. (Box 416, Folder 2)
- Index: VA1. Instr.Units-Sch.ofArch.& Urb.Plan.-Gen.,Admin.,& Budget(inc.:Turnover Savings, Japan/UCLA Exch.Prog.in Arch.)., 1987-1990. (Box 416, Folder 3)
- Index: VA1-03. Instr. Units - Sch. of Arch. & Urb. Planning - Gen., Admin., & Budget - Self Review (Follow-up to 5yr Review of Dean)., 1989-1993. (Box 416, Folder 4)
- Index: VA1-05. Instr. Units - School of Arch. & Urban Planning - General, Administration & Budget - P.R. - Proposed Restructuring., 1993. (Box 416, Folder 5)
- Index: VA1. Instr. Units-School of Architecture & Urban Planning-General, Admin. & Budget (inc.-04 Proposed Restructuring)., 1991-1996. (Box 417, Folder 1)